[Music]
Good evening gentlemen, and welcome to
the 2027 introductory video for the club.
2026 was a very successful year for us.
We played in 307 games,
and we won 207 of them.
But most importantly, after seven years
of playing together, we did it.
We won our first club finals championship.
What a way to cap off the year.
We had some very impressive
individual performances for the season
itself.
To start with, a Breakout Player of
the Year and top defenseman, Gotta Be.
Next, between the pipes every year, Jene
Rene
got the best Goalkeeper of the Year award.
After him, Slobby Robby, he won
Unsung Hero of the Year award,
picking up what needs to be picked up
when no one else is gonna do it.
And finally, leading the club in
almost every single category, setting
records
for the club, our MVP, Xavier Laflamme.
26 gave us a lot to build on.
We're ready to see what's next in 27.
And with the new year, as always, we're
changing.
New season, new look, and new leadership.
[Music continues]
Starting with our captain, wearing the
C this year will be Xavier Laflamme.
Joining him as assistant captain this year,
it will be Matt Hut.
And finally, the announcement we've been
waiting for,
our new jerseys for the NHL 2027 year.
Here they are.
[Music continues]
[On screen: HOME — teal jersey]
[On screen: AWAY — white jersey]
[On screen: ALTERNATE — purple jersey]
[On screen: Home, Away and Alternate
uniforms]
[On screen: LAST YEAR, WE MADE HISTORY.]
[On screen: THIS YEAR, WE DEFEND IT.]
[On screen: BARDOWNSKI HOCKEY CLUB]
[www.bardownski.hockey]
[Music fades]